SAMUEL ARANDIA

SYSTEMS ANALYSIS AND PROGRAMMING TECHNICIAN

ABOUT ME

I am a systems analysis and programming technician with one year of experience, trained to perform the software development cycle, incorporating requirements analysis, design, programming, testing and implementation of solutions, as well as their maintenance. Trained to meet the technical quality standards and requirements assigned. My skills include logical thinking, teamwork, written communication and selflearning. I am looking for a challenging and dynamic position to continue adding experience and knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

ELEVA SPA, April 2022- July 2022

- Perform Front-end and Back-end activities.
- Give daily reports of the activities performed
- Code the assigned requirements
- -Test finished projects and report bugs.

Web Developer Intern

ELEVAS SPA, January 2022 - April 2022

- Perform Front-end and Back-end activities
- Give daily reports of the activities performed
- Code the assigned requirements

EDUCATION

Platzi

Web development school

· January 2022 - Currently

Aiep Professional Institute (Chile)

Systems analysis and programming technician

- Unanimously approved and highest distinction
- March 2020 May 2022

Santiago Mariño Polytechnic University Institute (Venezuela)

Systems engineering

- August 2016 - April 2018 (5 semesters)

Universidad de oriente UDO (Venezuela)

Petroleum engineering

- August 2014 - April 2018 (5 semesters)

SKILLS

HTML5

CSS

- React
- Angular
- Javascript Python
- Vuejs
- PostgreSQL
- Django
- Git

Pug

- Django rest framework
- Vs code
- Boostrap
- Vuetify

- Code clean
- Methodology kanban
- Spanish
- Bitbucket y GitHub

CONTACT

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/samuel-arandia

email: samuelarandia@gmail.com

Phone: (+56) 9 7413 1158

Github: github.com/samuelArandia





Instituto Profesional

Por cuanto

Samuel Lorenzo Arandia Figuera

Ha cumplido los requisitos prescritos para obtener el título de **Técnico De Nivel Superior En Programación y Análisis De Sistemas** Aprobado Por Unanimidad y Máxima Distinción

Se le otorga este diploma en Santiago, a 3 de Mayo de 2022.



Secretario General

M. Fernan'
Rectora

Folio: 197568